# Tim Phillips, Designer

#### **About**

I'm a designer with an intrinsic passion for creating intuitive experiences and the underlying systems that enable them. I believe all problems can be solved when focusing on the users within the given problem space.

Throughout my process, I work horizontally across research, design, engineering and business. This allows me to constantly adapt and iterate, ensuring the final outcome is aligned, tested and proven.

#### Contact

Email timphillips1991@gmail.com
Web timphillipsdesign.com.au
Phone +61 409 888 443

#### Education

## Swinburne University of Technology

- Bachelor Design (Communication Design) (2012)
- Diploma of Graphic Design
   (2010 2011)

### Skills

Lo/Hi-fi mockups, Design thinking, Prototyping, Concept ideation, Usability testing, User research, Interaction design, Visual design, Wireframing

## Resume

## Experience

#### Carsales (2021 - present)

I'm currently working as the product designer in the carsales SELECT team, designing their consumer facing product across web and native platforms. The SELECT project aims to enable consumers to complete more parts of the car buying journey online.

#### **Assembler** (2020 - 2021)

I worked as the Lead Product Designer for Assembler. Leading the design across their range of platforms, as well as creating their design system. I also supported the engineering team with front-end web development.

### PwC Australia (2018 - 2020)

Working within PwC Australia's
New Ventures unit, I led the product
design and front-end web development
within the Automation Engine team.
We worked on a platform used by
internal teams, that enabled them
to build and manage web applications.

# The Just Group (2017 - 2018)

Predominantly worked on the Smiggle brand, designing web and email content for their global market base (AU, UK, IRE and Asia at the time). Also working across the Just Group's other core brands in varying capacities.

View prior experience (2016 - 2011)